email-gallery.com 2004-06-06

# Email-Gallery

**Privacy Policy**

This Privacy Policy outlines the information gathering and dissemination practices for this web site. It represents our privacy commitment to you. It is a work in progress. From time to time, as we expand our services, we will update our Privacy Policy, but the underlying goal of protecting our members' privacy will remain. We also welcome your continuous input into these guidelines. Give us your feedback at [webmaster@email-gallery.com](mailto:webmaster@email-gallery.com). 

email-gallery is a direct marketer that delivers targeted messages to its members. email-gallery is about getting permission from its subscribers to send them information on the topics that are relevant to them, not spam. All members of the email-gallery community have requested that they receive information related to specific topics. When working with its merchants, email-gallery reserves the right to review and edit outgoing messages to ensure messages are delivered to members who have requested such information. Users may unsubscribe to electronic mailings sent by us at any time by following the instructions contained at the end of every email-gallery newsletter or mailing. Users wishing to unsubscribe from email-gallery messages can also send a message to [webmaster@email-gallery.com](mailto:webmaster@email-gallery.com). 

email-gallery gathers personally identifiable information about users (such as name, postal address, email address, gender, date of birth, interests, other demographic information, etc.). By registering with email-gallery, you agree to allow us to share such personally identifiable information with advertisers, third party marketers and our affiliates for their direct and online marketing. This information will allow these parties to tailor a message to better match your likely interests. Though we are selective as to whom we partner, we do not control the practices of our marketing partners. 

email-gallery or its marketing partners may enhance or merge your personally identifiable information with data collected from other sources to use in direct or online marketing, including the data services described below. All information voluntarily provided to email-gallery by a registrant may be used to support our marketing partner’s data services business. These services include the provision of personally identifiable data to marketing companies, advertising agencies, data compilers, data companies, and, to the extent permitted by law, individual reference and look-up service programs. Such information may be used by such companies to provide users with information on products and services that may be of interest to them. 

If users indicate that they do not want to have their data shared with our marketing partners so that such marketing partners can make users aware of their product offerings, our marketing partners have agreed to limit the use of their data to the suppression, validation and enhancement of existing information held by third parties about its users. If users do not agree with the terms of this privacy policy, they have the option to choose not to be contacted or to have their information shared by terminating their email-gallery account at any time. 

This site has security measures in place to ensure against the loss, misuse, or alteration of information under our control. email-gallery protects the integrity and security of its data by following industry-standard procedures and guidelines. Only key executives and members of the development team at email-gallery possess the passwords required to access files requiring security clearances. 

The web pages at [www.email-gallery.com](http://www.email-gallery.com/) and some of the email sent by email-gallery contain links to external sites beyond our control. While we try to ensure that these other sites' Privacy Statements conform to our own, email-gallery can not represent or guarantee that they do so. Any site linked to the email-gallery site may have a Privacy Statement that differs from our own. 

If you have any questions regarding the policies of this site or your dealings with this site, please send email to [webmaster@email-gallery.com](mailto:webmaster@email-gallery.com).
